let musics = [
    {
      numb: 1,
      question: "Which of the following is not a type of music notation?",
      answer: "Morse code notation",
      options: ["Standard notation", "Tab notation", "Morse code notation", "Graphics notation"]
      
      
    },
    {
      numb: 2,
      question: "What is the most common time signature in classical music?",
      answer: "4/4",
      options: ["3/4", "4/4", "5/4", "6/8"]
      
      
    },
    {
      numb: 3,
      question: "Which of the following is not a type of instrument in a symphony orchestra?",
      answer: "Theremin",
      options: ["Violin", "Piano", "Harp", "Theremin"]
      
      
    },
    {
      numb: 4,
      question: "What is the most common key in pop music?",
      answer: "C Major",
      options: ["C Major", "G Major", "D Major", "A Major"]
      
      
    },
    {
      numb: 5,
      question: "Which of the following is not a type of chord?",
      answer: "Flat",
      options: ["Major", "Minor", "Diminished", "Flat"]
      
      
    },
    {
      numb: 6,
      question: "Which of the following is not a type of music genre?",
      answer: "Applesauce",
      options: ["Jazz", "Blues", "Rock", "Applesauce"]
      
      
    },
    {
      numb: 7,
      question: "Which of the following is not a type of music theory?",
      answer: "Cooking",
      options: ["Harmony", "Counterpoint", "Form", "Cooking"]
      
      
    },
    {
      numb: 8,
      question: "What is the most common tempo marking in classical music?",
      answer: "Allegro",
      options: ["Allegro", "Andante", "Adagio", "Moderato"]
      
      
    },
    {
      numb: 9,
      question: "Which of the following is not a type of musical form?",
      answer: "Spaghetti",
      options: ["Sonata", "Symphony", "Concerto", "Spaghetti"]
      
      
    },
    {
      numb: 10,
      question: "Which of the following is not a type of music notation software?",
      answer: "Microsoft Word",
      options: ["Sibelius", "Finale", "MuseScore", "Microsoft Word"]
      
      
    },
  ];